Irish Broadside Ballades BPP 1001
University of Notre Dame Rare Books & Special Collections
- "A New Song on the Release of the Political Prisoners", 1860; BPP 1001-255 (Box 4, Folder 247)
- "Rev. Father Tom, O'Neill", undated; BPP 1001-256 (Box 4, Folder 248)
- "The Riches of Ireland", undated; BPP 1001-257 (Box 4, Folder 249)
- "The Riggs and Sprees of Playhouse Square and Wapping", undated; BPP 1001-258 (Box 4, Folder 250)
- "Rights of Man", undated; BPP 1001-259 (Box 4, Folder 251)
- "The River Roe", undated; BPP 1001-260 (Box 4, Folder 252)
- "The Robber Outwitted", undated; BPP 1001-261 (Box 4, Folder 253)
- "A New Song on the Royal Visit", undated; BPP 1001-262 (Box 4, Folder 254)
- "A Dialogue Between a Schoolmaster and Laborer", 1860; BPP 1001-263 (Box 4, Folder 255)
- "Most Tragic Lines Written on the Seduction and Lamentable Death of Anny Gray", 1867; BPP 1001-264 (Box 4, Folder 256)
- "A New Song Called the Sewing Machine", undated; BPP 1001-265 (Box 4, Folder 257)
- "The Shamrock Green" and "Blow the Candle Out", undated; BPP 1001-266 (Box 4, Folder 258)
- "Shelling Green Peas", 1868; BPP 1001-267 (Box 4, Folder 259)
- "A Sight for a Father", undated; BPP 1001-268 (Box 4, Folder 260)
- "The Single Young Man Lodger", undated; BPP 1001-269 (Box 4, Folder 261)
- "For Sixteen Months I Courted Her", undated; BPP 1001-270 (Box 4, Folder 262)
- "The Skipper and Boy" and "Sodger Laddie", undated; BPP 1001-271 (Box 4, Folder 263)
- "The Sorrowful Lamentation of Andrew Carr who was Executed on the 28 of July at Richmond Jail For the Murder of Margret Murphy", 1860; BPP 1001-272 (Box 4, Folder 264)
- "A Sorrowful Lamentation on the Execution of Patrick Power who Suffered at the Front of Wexford Jail on the 4th of April for the Unnatural Murder of his Father", 1867; BPP 1001-273 (Box 4, Folder 265)
- "A Sorrowful Lamentation on the Hollywood Tragedy where Two Sisters Have Been Brutally Murdered", 1867; BPP 1001-274 (Box 4, Folder 265)
- "Speak of a Man as We Find Him" and "Bloom of Erin", 1855-1861; BPP 1001-275 (Box 4, Folder 266)
- "A New Song on the Sporting Races of Cavan", undated; BPP 1001-276 (Box 4, Folder 267)
- "A New Song on the Sporting Races of Kanturk", 1871; BPP 1001-277 (Box 4, Folder 268)
- "Spotted Cow", 1853-1879; BPP 1001-278 (Box 4, Folder 269)
- "The Star of Slane" and "General Burke's Dream", undated; BPP 1001-279 (Box 4, Folder 270)
- "The Strike" and "Tramp! Tramp, Tramp", undated; BPP 1001-281 (Box 4, Folder 271)
- "Surrender of Napoleon and France Determined", 1871; BPP 1001-282 (Box 4, Folder 272)
- "The Sweet Silver Light, Bonny Moon" and "Beautiful Bells", undated; BPP 1001-283 (Box 4, Folder 273)
- "Tara's Old Hall", undated; BPP 1001-284 (Box 4, Folder 274)
- "A New Song on the Taking Down of the Irish Census", 1871; BPP 1001-285 (Box 4, Folder 275)
- "Terence's Farewell", 1860; BPP 1001-286 (Box 4, Folder 276)
- "Terence's Farewell" and "Irish Boy", undated; BPP 1001-287 (Box 4, Folder 277)
- "There are Kind Hearts Everywhere" and "Just to Show There's No Ill-Feeling", circa 1859-1866; BPP 1001-288 (Box 4, Folder 278)
- "There was a Man Named O'Sullivan Lived Near Kildare", undated; BPP 1001-289 (Box 4, Folder 279)
- "Things I Do Like to See" and "The Cachuca", circa 1860-1873; BPP 1001-290 (Box 4, Folder 280)
- "A New Song Called the Three Huntsmen's Tragedy", 1868; BPP 1001-291 (Box 4, Folder 281)
- "A New and Much Admired Song called the Three Lovers' Trip to Carrickmagat By Michael Daily", undated; BPP 1001-292 (Box 4, Folder 282)
- "A Much Admired Song Called Tie My Toes to the Bed", undated; BPP 1001-293 (Box 4, Folder 283)
- "A New Song on the Tipperary Ass" (Copy 1), 1869; BPP 1001-294 (Box 4, Folder 284)
- "A New Song on the Tipperary Ass" (Copy 2), 1869; BPP 1001-295 (Box 4, Folder 285)
- "Tipperary Man's Courtship", 1860; BPP 1001-296 (Box 4, Folder 286)
- "Tramp! Tramp!! Tramp!!!", 1868; BPP 1001-297 (Box 4, Folder 287)
- "The True-Lover's Trip over the Mountain", undated; BPP 1001-298 (Box 4, Folder 288)
- "A True History of Bernard Reilly, a Returned Convict who was Transported in the Year 1824", undated; BPP 1001-299 (Box 4, Folder 289)
- "A New Song on Unconquered Tipperary", undated; BPP 1001-300 (Box 4, Folder 290)
- "Up in a Balloon", 1867; BPP 1001-301 (Box 4, Folder 291)
- "We Are Coming Sister Mary" and "My Bonny Lad Is Young But He's Growing", 1863-1885; BPP 1001-302 (Box 4, Folder 292)
- "We Miss Thee at Home," "Bonny Eloise," and "The Dear Little Shamrock", undated; BPP 1001-303 (Box 4, Folder 293)
- "A New Song Called the Wedding Afternoon", undated; BPP 1001-304 (Box 4, Folder 294)
- "Wedding of Balyporeen" and "The Stage Struck Hero", undated; BPP 1001-305 (Box 4, Folder 295)
- "On the Wexford Man of '98", undated; BPP 1001-306 (Box 4, Folder 296)
- "What Can the Matter Be" and "Steam's Up Darkies", undated; BPP 1001-307 (Box 4, Folder 297)
- "Where are the Friends of my Youth?," "Rock Me to Sleep, Mother," "What Can a Porr Maiden Do?," and "The Old Oaken Bucket", circa 1863-1885; BPP 1001-308 (Box 4, Folder 298)
- "William and Eliza; Or, Lough Eene Shor", undated; BPP 1001-309 (Box 4, Folder 299)
- "New Song Called William and Jane on the Banks of Clyde", undated; BPP 1001-310 (Box 4, Folder 300)
- "A New Song on William O'Brien and the 'Mysterious Rats'", undated; BPP 1001-311 (Box 4, Folder 301)
- "A New Song Called Willy Leonard", undated; BPP 1001-312 (Box 4, Folder 302)
- "Willy Reilly and his Dear Colleen Bawn", undated; BPP 1001-313 (Box 4, Folder 303)
- "The Window", undated; BPP 1001-314 (Box 4, Folder 304)
- "A New Song Called Wire In and Get Your Tea Pot", undated; BPP 1001-315 (Box 4, Folder 305)
- "A New Song Called the Wonders of the World", 1868; BPP 1001-316 (Box 4, Folder 306)
- "Work, Boys, Work," and "The Irish Excavator", undated; BPP 1001-317 (Box 4, Folder 307)
- "Wrongs of Ireland", undated; BPP 1001-318 (Box 4, Folder 308)
- "You Never Can Tell", 1863-1885; BPP 1001-319 (Box 4, Folder 309)
- "An Admired Song Called Youghal Harbour", undated; BPP 1001-320 (Box 4, Folder 310)
- "Young Henry of the Raging Main" and "Erin is my Home", undated; BPP 1001-321 (Box 4, Folder 311)
- "A New Song Called the Young Lady's Lamentation for the Loss of Her True Love", undated; BPP 1001-322 (Box 4, Folder 312)
- "A New Song Called the Young Man in Search of his Sister", undated; BPP 1001-323 (Box 4, Folder 313)
- "A New Song Called the Young Squire or the Counselor Outwitted", 1860; BPP 1001-324 (Box 4, Folder 314)
- "Young Volunteer! on his March to Battle", undated; BPP 1001-325 (Box 4, Folder 315)
- "Young Woman's Wants," and "Reading Made Easy", undated; BPP 1001-326 (Box 4, Folder 316)
- "A New Song on the Afghan War", undated; BPP 1001-001-F2 (Box 5, Folder 317)
- "A New Song on the Curragh Murder", undated; BPP 1001-002-F2 (Box 5, Folder 318)
- "A New Song on the Erecting of O'Connell's Monument For 1882", BPP 1001-003-F2 (Box 5, Folder 319)
- "Lamentable Lines on the Execution of the Maamtrasna Murderers", 1884?; BPP 1001-004-F2 (Box 5, Folder 320)
- "Our Latest Song - The Gems of the Land League. Air- The Gems of Old Ireland", undated; BPP 1001-005-F2 (Box 5, Folder 321)
- "A New Song on the Happy Return of Moody and Sankey", undated; BPP 1001-006-F2 (Box 5, Folder 322)
- "Lamentable Lines on Joe. Brady and Dan. Curley", 1882; BPP 1001-007-F2 (Box 5, Folder 323)
- "Joseph Brady's Last Advice to the People of Ireland", undated; BPP 1001-008-F2 (Box 5, Folder 324)
- "McKenna's Dream", undated; BPP 1001-009-F2 (Box 5, Folder 325)
- "A New Song on the Massacre of 20,000 Roman Catholics in Syria", undated; BPP 1001-010-F2 (Box 5, Folder 326)
- "Lines on the Death of Miss Fanny Parnell. Air-Exile of Erin", undated; BPP 1001-011-F2 (Box 5, Folder 327)
- "Release of M. L. Davitt, (Founder of the Land League)", 1878; BPP 1001-012-F2 (Box 5, Folder 328)
- "Lines on the Phoenix Park Tragedy", 1882; BPP 1001-013-F2 (Box 5, Folder 329)
- "Poor Pat Must Emigrate. Air-'Apple Praters.'", undated; BPP 1001-014-F2 (Box 5, Folder 330)
- "Sights and Scenes of Dublin", undated; BPP 1001-015-F2 (Box 5, Folder 331)
- "The Star of Erin's Isle", undated; BPP 1001-016-F2 (Box 5, Folder 332)
- "The Surprising Tree of Knowledge", undated; BPP 1001-017-F2 (Box 5, Folder 333)